this tutorial is about using the
本教程是关于使用
V形折叠的特质创造出额外的
this tutorial is about using the
qualities of the v-fold to create extra
V型折叠将其关闭的高大结构
当你有一个向前折叠
qualities of the v-fold to create extra
tall structures as the v-fold closes it
浮在上面的水上飞机
靠近页面，然后您
tall structures as the v-fold closes it
folds down forwards when you have a
可以在其上构建另一个视图折叠
指向另一个方向
folds down forwards when you have a
floating plane built onto it that comes
降落乘坐另一架浮动飞机
再次降低到该页面，则可以
floating plane built onto it that comes
down nearer to the page and so then you
在此基础上构建，因此您可以构建一个
通过构建这些曲折效果
down nearer to the page and so then you
can build another view fold on it
反向指向B折叠，所以这是一个
我制作的非常原始的版本，我会
can build another view fold on it
pointing in the other direction and that
一分钟告诉你我是怎么做到的
在那之前，我只是喜欢经历
pointing in the other direction and that
comes down taking another floating plane
有些书真的很棒
首先是它们中的高默认结构
comes down taking another floating plane
again lower to the page then you can
我想告诉你的书是大卫
佩勒姆（Pelham）像丽莎（Lisa）的微风，
again lower to the page then you can
build onto that and so you can build a
一个非常惊人的结构
结束，这是这些塔之一
build onto that and so you can build a
sort of zigzag effect by building these
如果你从后面看它的结构
您可以在这里看到v形折叠
sort of zigzag effect by building these
reverse pointing B folds so this is a
倒下站起来，这提高了
这里有其他的浮动飞机
reverse pointing B folds so this is a
pretty crude version I made and I'll
基于它的V形折叠很难
实际上看到它，但是在这里你可以
pretty crude version I made and I'll
show you how I made this in a minute but
看到这是另一个V型折叠和双臂
附在那些飞机上突出
show you how I made this in a minute but
before that I just like to run through
而这在最顶端，您可以
看到这是一个V型折，另一个V型折
before that I just like to run through
some books that have really amazingly
在它上面，然后这个脸是一个
平行泡沫，所以不错的设计
some books that have really amazingly
tall default structures in them first
下一个我想告诉你的是
这是一个非常非凡的身材
tall default structures in them first
book I'd like to show you is David
结构，我们不可能
在本教程中解释它，但我只是
book I'd like to show you is David
Pelham's like a Lisa breeze and it's got
以为你真的很想看这个
一种上升到如此高的方式
Pelham's like a Lisa breeze and it's got
a really amazing structure at the very
气泡页面，如果我们看一下
您可以看到它背后的结构是
a really amazing structure at the very
end this is one of these tower
此处的V形折叠浮起水上飞机
这里，但实际测量
end this is one of these tower
structures if you look at it from behind
在这边和这边测量
这几天很复杂
structures if you look at it from behind
you can see in here there is a v-fold
所以只享受高度和你的未来
将来的工作，所以我们将对其进行解释，然后
you can see in here there is a v-fold
goes down stands up that is raising a
我们有这个，这是另一本书
由Matthew Reinhart丛林书另一本
goes down stands up that is raising a
floating plane here which has got other
非凡的传播在这里又是它
在页面上方真的很高
floating plane here which has got other
v-folds built on it it's hard to
是v折
这些是由
v-folds built on it it's hard to
actually see into it but here you can
你向后看，你可以看到
一组平行四边形和人
actually see into it but here you can
see this is another V fold and the arms
举起这具
又有一个v-fold
see this is another V fold and the arms
are attached to those planes jutting out
还有就是这样
持续不断的互动
are attached to those planes jutting out
and this at the very top well you can
基于v形折叠的事实
向下前进给你一架飞机
and this at the very top well you can
see this is a v-fold with another V fold
然后您就可以继续前进
和更高，所以你最终得到一个
see this is a v-fold with another V fold
on top of it and then this the face is a
比总数高的结构
书页的高度，因此
on top of it and then this the face is a
parallel foam so yeah nice design
下一个这是一个非常小的
菲利普·弗朗西（书本）
parallel foam so yeah nice design
the next one I'd like to show you is
预订它真的是很棒的颜色，但是
我唯一想向你展示的是
the next one I'd like to show you is
this is a really extraordinary tall
一个是这个小弹出窗口
出现了惊人的高
this is a really extraordinary tall
structure that there's no way we could
考虑页面的大小，这是
即将出现的V型折叠
structure that there's no way we could
explain it in this tutorial but I just
效果这是一个浮动飞机，但是
基于两个的尺寸
explain it in this tutorial but I just
thought you'd really like to see this
立柱，这就是给
你那惊人的身高，然后
thought you'd really like to see this
one the way it rises up so high above
最后一个我想给你看这些
弹出科学怪人和这篇论文
one the way it rises up so high above
the bubble page if we look at the
工程，这是大卫·霍克（David Hawk）
这类似于我的最后一个
the bubble page if we look at the
structure behind that you can see it is
给你看，但更多
你得到的非凡身高
structure behind that you can see it is
a v-fold here raising a floating plane
这个谚语再次基于v折
默认折叠向前给你这个
a v-fold here raising a floating plane
here but the the actual measurements the
等效于
另一个坠落在上面，但这是一个
here but the the actual measurements the
measurements at this side and this side
有点复杂和复杂
比那更多的是，这就是全部
measurements at this side and this side
and on these days is quite complicated
我想带你看书，然后
我只会告诉你如何制作
and on these days is quite complicated
so just enjoy the height and your future
其中之一的简化​​版本
非常彻底地从底片开始
so just enjoy the height and your future
future work so we'll explain it and then
弄皱，然后我已经预先切好了
这些是新褶皱，我认为是
future work so we'll explain it and then
we've got this one this is another book
教程二是直角V折
所以他们只是在中间折痕
we've got this one this is another book
by Matthew Reinhart jungle book another
它们都在底部90度
我们要去的顶部和底部的标签
by Matthew Reinhart jungle book another
extraordinary spread here it is again it
贴在这里和整个事情上
将向前折叠，并且有
extraordinary spread here it is again it
comes up really high above the page this
将会是另一个
所以整个事情都会往前走，
comes up really high above the page this
is a v-fold
将浮动平面放在其顶部，
你可以得到最大的运动是
is a v-fold
these are parallelograms being raised by
你越靠近脊椎90度
运动越多，
these are parallelograms being raised by
it you look behind and you can see it's
闪光一点点，但如果你90岁
整个脊椎度
it you look behind and you can see it's
an array of parallelograms and people
只是跌落，所以你不能90岁
度，你必须上升像
an array of parallelograms and people
raising this floating plane which has
像这样的85
你从一面向下开始
raising this floating plane which has
got another v-fold
我要像我一样接近90度
可以与脊柱90度贴合吗
got another v-fold
and another so that's how you get this
向下折叠，然后关闭底座，然后折叠
找到它的自然黏附位置
and another so that's how you get this
sort of constant interaction that's all
这是第一个V螺栓，我们想要
下一个它需要被卡住
sort of constant interaction that's all
based on the fact that the v-fold folds
与之平行，所以我只用它
小卡片给我
based on the fact that the v-fold folds
down forwards which gives you a plane
保证平行线粘贴
有一条线我们只是坚持下去
down forwards which gives you a plane
that you can then build on and go higher
方面，我会保留以备将来参考
所以我们再次将其粘贴到花键上
that you can then build on and go higher
and higher so you end up with a
中央折痕对齐的线
脊椎折叠关闭，我们必须
and higher so you end up with a
structure which is higher than the total
这里要非常小心，因为我们有
另一个已经就位
structure which is higher than the total
height of the page of the book so the
有两个相同的V形折叠，现在我们
可以在上面放一个浮动飞机
height of the page of the book so the
next one this is a very pretty little
所以就拿其中一件吧
应该是正确的，你可以永远
next one this is a very pretty little
book big bang pop by philip foo french
贴上后修剪
所以你只需要放置
book big bang pop by philip foo french
book it's really amazing colors but the
尺寸合适，中间有折痕
弄好它，确保
book it's really amazing colors but the
only thing i wanted to show you in this
这将适合所有这四个
标签，您可以将胶水粘在
only thing i wanted to show you in this
one is is this little pop-up that that
同时把它放到位
折叠它的喊叫声，以确保全部
one is is this little pop-up that that
comes up amazingly high for the
工作很好，我们去了，那就是
第一个电镀平面关闭时，您会看到
comes up amazingly high for the
considering the size of the page this is
它下降了，给了我们
在折痕和外边缘之间
considering the size of the page this is
a v-fold that's coming forward and in
我们有足够的空间玩
所以现在我们可以在
a v-fold that's coming forward and in
effect this is a floating plane but the
那个
所以这次我们将在V文件空间
effect this is a floating plane but the
dimensions on the base on the two
相反的方式，所以他们将
面对这些以前的标签
dimensions on the base on the two
uprights and on this that's what gives
我让他们面对如此
这意味着最好的观看方式
uprights and on this that's what gives
you that amazing height and then the
这个结构就是这样
我将再次制作标签
you that amazing height and then the
last one I wanted to show you these
尽管V指向这个方向
将标签指向我
last one I wanted to show you these
pop-up Frankenstein and the paper
以便您获得更好的视觉效果
当你看着它，我会坚持下去
pop-up Frankenstein and the paper
engineering and this is by David Hawk
一只粘在一张幻灯片上将其关闭
那是第二层的开始
engineering and this is by David Hawk
and this is similar to the last one I
这个需要再次被卡住
与此平行，所以我将使用它
and this is similar to the last one I
showed you but it's even more
模板再次标记
浮动飞机只需要做一个
showed you but it's even more
extraordinary height that you get
因为另一面将要
找到它的自然位置就可以了
extraordinary height that you get
this proverb again it's based on v-folds
仔细关闭它，或者
不太正确，所以我们一直坚持下去
this proverb again it's based on v-folds
default folding forward giving you this
在此之上的另一层让我们来看
如果那个人适合这样一个想法
default folding forward giving you this
equivalent of a floating playing with
在上面加一个折痕，然后在所有上面涂胶
这些拍打在那个角落的后面
equivalent of a floating playing with
another befall built onto it but it's a
把它放进去
在那里，我们已经分层了
another befall built onto it but it's a
bit more complicated and sophisticated
所以他仍然介于那沟壑和
外率，所以应该有空间
bit more complicated and sophisticated
than that so that's that one this is all
第三课，让我们尝试一下
这张卡有点轻
than that so that's that one this is all
I wanted to show you in books and then
这会有点重，
坚固一点，但我们再放一个
I wanted to show you in books and then
I'll just show you how to make a sort of
再次面对这一点
是的，仍然工作，它仍然停留
I'll just show you how to make a sort of
simplified version of one of these we
在外页中，这样我们就可以得到
与之平行的下一层
simplified version of one of these we
start with a base sheet very thoroughly
好
仍在或多或少地摇晃
start with a base sheet very thoroughly
creased and then I've got these pre-cut
我们将在此之上再增加一层
这四个选项卡上均为蓝色，正好适合
creased and then I've got these pre-cut
new folds these are I think it was
在里面关闭它是
上升到三个水平
new folds these are I think it was
tutorial two it's the right angle V fold
摇摇欲坠摇摇欲坠
无论如何，这个想法仍然很多
tutorial two it's the right angle V fold
so they're just crease down the middle
大于页面的实际大小
它从那里升起，你仍然
so they're just crease down the middle
they're both 90 degrees at the bottom
在这里和外部之间有间隙
页面，因此您仍然可以放置一个新文件夹
they're both 90 degrees at the bottom
tabs on the top and bottom we're going
最重要的是让我们尝试
这样的一个，所以我会把它变成一个
tabs on the top and bottom we're going
to stick it on here and the whole thing
这次急性三倍的角度
中间不到90岁的夫妻
to stick it on here and the whole thing
is going to fold forward and there's
的标签只有一点一二
完成所有工作并充分利用
is going to fold forward and there's
going to be another one in front of it
我们设法产生的高度
这将再次指向
going to be another one in front of it
so the whole thing can fall forwards and
回到我这是这样的
也许我会在上面放一个柜台折
so the whole thing can fall forwards and
hold a floating plane on top of it and
稍微折叠一下就可以了
这样，这就是你有一个
hold a floating plane on top of it and
you can get the maximum movement is the
您可以看到四级弹出结构
我们的目标是更多的想法
you can get the maximum movement is the
closer you go to 90 degrees to the spine
硬卡会有所帮助
精确测量有助于
closer you go to 90 degrees to the spine
the more movement you'll get and the
总体而言，您对我们的想法有所了解
尝试做，我们有点结构
the more movement you'll get and the
flash little going but if you go at 90
比原始页面大很多
在我正在努力的时候内置
flash little going but if you go at 90
degrees to the spine the whole thing
一本关于高度复杂的弹出式设计的书
那应该在某个时候出版
degrees to the spine the whole thing
just falls flat so you can't go at 90
在2018年
您
just falls flat so you can't go at 90
degrees you have to go up something like